[{"question": "  hey pheebs?", "answer": " huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " i&#146;m having dinner with my dad tomorrow night, do you wanna come?", "answer": " sure. yeah, he&#146;s kinda sexy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " oh no, no, i&#146;ll be there too.", "answer": " okay so, we&#146;ll just come up with some kind of signal if it&#146;s going well you can take off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " no phoebe! i just need you there for support. i haven&#146;t told him i&#146;m pregnant yet.", "answer": " oh. why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " &#145;cause i know he&#146;s gonna flip out and i hate it when he&#146;s angry.", "answer": " oh rachel, this is all so &#145;papa don&#146;t preach.&#146;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " what phoebe? wait! one time he caught me smoking he said if he ever saw me doing that again he&#146;d make me eat the entire pack.", "answer": " wow! oh well, i will be there!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " gosh. i&#146;m not gonna let that man make you eat your baby.  oh. hey! who is that guy? i think i know him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": "  no you don&#146;t!", "answer": "  no you don&#146;t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " oh my god!!! monica!! he&#146;s the stripper from your bachelorette party!!", "answer": " her what?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " your secret bachelorette party&#133;", "answer": " you had a bachelorette party?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " she untied his g-string with her teeth.  somebody stop me!", "answer": " i thought we weren&#146;t gonna have bachelor/bachelorette parties! y&#146;know, we agreed that it was a silly tradition.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " it&#146;s a grand tradition!", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry, they surprised me. there was nothing i could do!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " well you could&#146;ve untied it with your hands.", "answer": " this is so unfair! the one thing i wanted to do was throw my best friend a bachelor party, but no, i wasn&#146;t allowed to. all i got was a stupid steak dinner!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " you went home with the waitress.", "answer": " oh yeah, that was a pretty good night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe you didn&#146;t tell me! you know that the two pillars of marriage are openness and honesty!", "answer": " ugh, i knew giving you that book was gonna come back and bite me in the ass!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " how about i order everyone the moroccan chicken?", "answer": " oh, i-i don&#146;t eat meat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " it&#146;s chicken.", "answer": " yeah, i don&#146;t eat that either.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " i&#146;ll never understand you lesbians.  so baby, tell me&#133;what is new with you.", "answer": " well actually umm&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": "  your &#146;74 lafite sir.", "answer": " &#146;74?! i ordered the &#146;75! that&#146;s a magnificent wine! the &#146;74 is sewage! why would you bring me sewage?!  is that a hard question? are you an idiot? is that why you&#146;re a waiter?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": "  in case you didn&#146;t notice, that is a scary man.", "answer": " he&#146;s right though, the &#146;74 is absolute piss.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " this was such a huge mistake. i can&#146;t tell him phoebe. i can&#146;t, i can&#146;t, i can&#146;t, i can&#146;t&#133;", "answer": " rachel!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " no it&#146;s okay, this is what&#146;s gonna happen. i&#146;m gonna wait a couple years and then the baby will tell him.", "answer": " why, so he can get mad at the baby?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " hey, that is the&#133;baby&#146;s problem.  oh, everything okay with the waiter?", "answer": " i have no idea, i went to the bathroom. so sweetie, you were starting to tell me what is uh, what is new with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " well&#133; umm, i got tivo.", "answer": " what&#146;s tivo?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " it&#146;s slang for pregnant.", "answer": " phoebe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " are you really pregnant?", "answer": " well uh, yes and no. except not no. so to sum it up, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " no, it&#146;s ross. it&#146;s ross. you like ross.  oh daddy, i hope you&#146;re okay with all of this. i mean think about it, this is a good thing. you&#146;re gonna&#151;this is your first grandchild! you&#146;re gonna be a poppy!", "answer": " that&#146;s true.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": "  poppy.  oh, i&#146;m gonna be a poppy.  so when is the wedding?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " who?", "answer": " the wedding! there&#146;s going to be a wedding. young lady, don&#146;t you sit there and tell me my first grandchild is going to be a bastard!  rachel karen green, tell me there is gonna be a wedding!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " so it was really cool seeing you lecture today.", "answer": " oh thanks. although it kinda seemed like you were falling asleep there a little.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " oh no-no, i-i had my eyes closed so i could concentrate and y&#146;know take it all in.", "answer": " yeah, a lot of my students do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " so, i gotta get going.", "answer": " okay, i-i&#146;ll see you tonight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " okay, bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " my god! you must be good in bed!", "answer": " so uh, you and mona, been a while now. how&#146;s it going?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " ah, it&#146;s good. it&#146;s going good. i mean, we get along great. she&#146;s, she&#146;s so&#133;", "answer": " hot?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " well, i was gonna say sweet, but yeah-huh!", "answer": " she&#146;s okay with rachel and the baby?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " well i&#133;i haven&#146;t actually told her yet. i don&#146;t want to scare her off, y&#146;know?", "answer": " well, you have to honest with her! otherwise you may think that you&#146;re going down the same path, but you&#146;re really going down different ones.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " i&#146;m gonna take that book and beat you to death with it.", "answer": "  oh my god! you are gonna love me so much! i felt really bad about the whole bachelorette party thing, so tonight you&#146;re gonna have a bachelor party.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " yeah, i got this number from this guy at work and i hired a stripper to come dance for you. am i going in the wife hall of fame or what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " honey! that&#146;s crazy! i don&#146;t want you to get me a stripper&#133;", "answer": " will you let the lady talk?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " come on! come on, it&#146;ll be fun! it&#146;ll make me feel so much better.", "answer": " look, i appreciate it, but uh, it&#146;s a little creepy. y&#146;know? i&#146;m not a bachelor anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " so don&#146;t think of it as a bachelor party, think of it as a&#133;a two month anniversary present.", "answer": " sure, one year is paper, but two months is lapdance!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " please! i feel so bad! just watch the hot woman get naked!", "answer": " all right fine! but i&#146;m only doing this for you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " and joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " thank you. all right, now who else do you want to invite?", "answer": " ah, no-no-no just ross. ross and joey is embarrassing enough.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " uh actually, sorry i can&#146;t even make it. i&#146;m seeing mona again tonight.", "answer": " i understand: who would cancel an actual date to go to a fake bachelor party?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry i won&#146;t be able to make it to your imaginary wedding, but i&#146;m really busy that day. yeah, i already have a unicorn baptism and a leprechaun bar mitzvah.", "answer": " i know. i know. i panicked, i panicked. i didn&#146;t want him to start yelling at me like i was some &#146;74 latour.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " it&#146;s lafite. the &#146;74 latour is actually drinking quite nicely.", "answer": " all right here he comes. i&#146;m gonna do this, i&#146;m gonna tell him, i&#146;m gonna be strong.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " i just called a friend of mine.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " i think i may be able to book the plaza on short notice.", "answer": " really?! the plaza?!! oh daddy!!  right. daddy, i need to talk to you. please, sit down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " what is it sweetie?", "answer": " there&#146;s not gonna be a wedding. ross and i are not getting married.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry daddy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " i don&#146;t believe this!!", "answer": " oh now daddy, stay calm. please.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " stay calm?!! how do you expect me to stay calm?! this is unacceptable rachel! and i wanna know why?!! is it because that punk ross won&#146;t marry you?! that&#146;s it! is that it?!", "answer": " yes. yes, he says i&#146;m damaged goods.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " so you uh, nervous about getting married?", "answer": " what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " look, look let&#146;s pretend it&#146;s a real bachelor party. okay? y&#146;know? before your wedding. come on, it&#146;ll be fun.", "answer": " okay. i can&#146;t believe tomorrow&#146;s the big day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " how does it feel knowing you&#146;re never gonna be with another woman again huh? knowing you&#146;re gonna have to wake up to the same face everyday until you finally have the sweet release of death.", "answer": " you&#146;re right, this is more fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " so which one of you lucky boys is chandler?", "answer": " uh, that-that&#146;s-that&#146;s me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " that&#146;s me.", "answer": " joey tribbiani, a big fan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " yeah, yeah right over there.", "answer": " all right, whenever you&#146;re ready.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " that was weird.", "answer": " why-why would she go in the bedroom?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " so she&#146;s a&#133;", "answer": " yeah, that&#146;s one naked hooker!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " uh that&#146;s an eighteenth century indian artifact from calcutta.", "answer": " oh wow! so, you&#146;re more than just dinosaurs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " oh my god! oh my god! i&#146;m so sorry!", "answer": " aw forget it, it&#146;s from pier one.  sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " you think you can knock up my daughter and then not marry her?! i&#146;m gonna kill you!!", "answer": " y&#146;know this is actually not a great time for me. commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " so? come on! explain yourself geller! first you get my rachel pregnant!", "answer": " you got rachel pregnant?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " who did?!", "answer": " you did!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " yes. yes, yes i did.  but-but it was, it was just a one night thing. it meant nothing.", "answer": " oh? really? that&#146;s what my daughter means to you? nothing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " no! no sir umm, she means a lot to me. i mean, i care&#151;i-i love rachel.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": "  oh but not that way. i mean&#133;i mean i&#146;m not in love with her. i love her like a, like a friend.", "answer": " oh really? that&#146;s how treat a friend? you get her in trouble and then refuse to marry her?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": "  hey! i offered to marry her!", "answer": " wh&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": "  but i didn&#146;t want to.", "answer": " well why not? so you can spend your time with this tramp?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " tramp?!", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry. dr. green, mona. mona, dr. green.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe there is a naked hooker in there!", "answer": " wait! wait! maybe she&#146;s a hooker and a stripper, but she got confused about what she&#146;s supposed to do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " could be. i mean technically she did strip, we just, we just missed it.  ma&#146;am, are you also a stripper?", "answer": " uh, no. but i could pretend to strip, but that&#146;s gonna cost extra. okay, here&#146;s the extras, handcuffs, spanking&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " maybe monica&#146;s playing a joke on ya. y&#146;know? getting her own husband a hooker, that&#146;s pretty funny.", "answer": " that is funny, maybe for my birthday she&#146;ll murder someone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " i bet ross was in on it too. i mean he was conveniently busy.", "answer": " do you mind if i smoke in here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " how could you have kept all of this from me?", "answer": " i was going to tell you, but&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " but what?! you figured you&#146;d get what you wanted and then dump her like you dumped rachel!", "answer": " hey! i did not dump rachel!  nor are we still together.  can i just&#133;  why don&#146;t we just let the machine get that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": "  hey ross. it&#146;s joey. there&#146;s a hooker over here and we thought maybe you&#146;d know something about it.", "answer": " no! no! no! no! no! i-i-i-i&#151;i need to, i need to lie down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " so, tonight&#146;s the night of the big bachelor party?", "answer": " yeah! hey! thanks for getting me that girl&#146;s number.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " no problem. so who&#146;s the party for?", "answer": " my husband.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " you hired your husband a hooker?", "answer": " she&#146;s a stripper.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " no, she&#146;s a hooker.", "answer": " is that, is that what they call strippers sometimes?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " when they&#146;re hookers.", "answer": " oh my god stu! i-i can&#146;t believe you did this! now are you absolutely sure she&#146;s a hooker?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " maybe she meant to get you a hooker.", "answer": " why would she do that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " maybe she wants you to learn something. huh? now is there anything you&#146;re really bad at y&#146;know, sexually?", "answer": " this is the worst bachelor party ever!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " what&#146;s taking you boys so long?", "answer": " in a minute!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": "  in a minute? what&#146;s gonna happen in a minute?!", "answer": " all right, all right maybe-maybe you should just ask her to leave.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " why me?!", "answer": " hey! it&#146;s your bachelor party.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " which is why you should do it.", "answer": " i don&#146;t want to. you do it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " you do it!", "answer": " you do it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " all right rock, paper, scissors who has to tell the whore to leave!  what?", "answer": " i miss this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " i don&#146;t think we&#146;ve actually done this before!", "answer": " no, i-i miss hanging out with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " well we&#133;we still hang out.", "answer": " not like we used to. remember? you and me used to be inseparable. y&#146;know now it&#146;s like&#133;things are different.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " well y&#146;know, things are different. i&#146;m&#133;i&#146;m married now.", "answer": " oh sure&#151;and hey, don&#146;t get me wrong, i am so happy for you guys. i just&#133;i miss&#133;hanging out&#133;just-just us, y&#146;know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " yeah, i miss that too. i tell you what; from now on we&#146;ll make time to hang out with each other.", "answer": " you got it. come here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " so your dad dropped by. he&#146;s a pleasant man!", "answer": "  oh no&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " i&#146;d better go.  just over here: i don&#146;t want to miss the fight.", "answer": " ross i&#146;m so sorry. okay. i-i will promise i will straighten this out with him tomorrow in person, or via e-mail.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " i don&#146;t care about your dad! i care about mona! she was there and now she&#146;s totally freaked out!", "answer": " oh okay, i&#146;ll fix that to. what&#146;s her e-mail address?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " rachel!", "answer": " all right, i promise. i&#146;ll fix this. i swear. i&#146;ll-i&#146;ll-i&#146;ll-i&#146;ll talk to her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " thank you!", "answer": " that&#146;s it?! you call that a fight? come on! &quot;we were on a break!&quot; &quot;no we weren&#146;t!&quot; what happened to you two?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " thank you so much for coming back over.", "answer": " oh good, you&#146;re here. yeah, and i was worried that it was going to be uncomfortable.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " i know mona, just hear me out. first of all, i&#146;m so sorry about my father yelling at you, but i heard you totally held your own. you&#146;re gonna have to tell me how you did that.", "answer": " focus.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " okay. um&#133;but&#151;okay, yes ross and i used to date. and yes we are gonna have a baby. but we are definitely not getting back together.", "answer": " how can i be sure on that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " oh we just&#151;we drove each other crazy!", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " i mean he was possessive, he was jealous, he could never just let the little things go!", "answer": " trying to date this woman.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " probably shouldn&#146;t touch me.", "answer": " y&#146;know, i-i-i just&#133;i don&#146;t want to get in the middle of something so complicated.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " should i leave this open for you too?", "answer": " i&#146;m not sure yet. why didn&#146;t you just tell me about all this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " because what&#146;s going on with rachel has nothing to do with how i feel about you.", "answer": " yeah? well you still shoulda told me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " i know and i was going to, but i thought it was better that you heard it from rachel&#146;s father. look i&#133;i made a mistake, but it&#146;s only because i really, really like you. really!", "answer": " okay, i guess you can&#133;close the door now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " i swear i didn&#146;t know she was a hooker! i mean wh&#151;did you let her smoke in here?", "answer": " her ass print is still on your grandmother&#146;s quilt, do you really want to talk about smoking?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " monica! wait!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " could you not narrate?", "answer": " gotcha sailor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": "  &#133;just because you&#146;re not in love with the guy you can&#146;t&#133;", "answer": "  wow, you told your dad the truth.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " about an hour ago.", "answer": " wanna go see a movie?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}]